http://www.ahp-dsg.com/en/terms-and-conditions

FR
Mega Menu (Main Site Tree)
FR
Top Menu (Mobile)
Terms and Conditions
The Domtar.com web Site and any other Domtar-linked site (each, a "Site") is an online information service where you can obtain information about products and services provided by Domtar Corporation or its affiliates (each, a “Group Company”), and is available subject to your compliance with the terms and conditions set forth below.  Nothing in this Site shall be construed as creating any warranty or other obligation on the part of Domtar Corporation or its Group Companies (collectively, “We” or "Us" or “Our”).
Agreement.  Please read the following information carefully before using this Site. By using this Site, you agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions. If you do not agree with any part of these Terms and Conditions, do not use this Site. We reserve the right, in Our sole discretion, to modify, alter or otherwise update these Terms and Conditions at any time, and by using this Site after the posting of a modification, you accept the modification.  Any changes will be effective only after the effective date of the change and will not affect any dispute arising prior to the effective date of the change. The effective date of this notice and any revised or changed notice may be found on this page, on the bottom left hand corner of the notice.  Any changes will be effective only after the effective date of the change and will not affect any dispute arising prior to the effective date of the change.
Disclaimer of Warranties; Limitation of Liability.  THIS SITE AND ITS CONTENTS ARE PROVIDED "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, OR NON-INFRINGEMENT AND WE SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIM ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES, WHETHER OF MERCHANTABILITY, SUITABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, INFRINGEMENT OR OTHERWISE.  These warranties are hereby excluded to the fullest extent permissible by law.  UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL WE BE LIABLE FOR ANY DIRECT OR INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, PUNITIVE, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES THAT MAY ARISE FROM YOUR USE OF, OR INABILITY TO USE, THIS SITE, including but not limited to, loss of profits, loss of use, loss of data or information, business interruption, or any other damages whether in an action of contract, negligence or other tortious action, arising out of or in connection with the availability, use, reliance on or inability to use any information available from this Site. In no event shall Our total liability for claims, damages and causes of action, whether in contract, tort or otherwise, exceed the amount paid by you, if any, for accessing this Site.  Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion or limitation of liability for consequential or incidental damages. In such jurisdictions, Our liability is limited to the greatest extent permitted by law, or $10, whichever is less.
We make no representations whatsoever about the suitability of the information contained in the documents, related graphics and materials published on this Site, for any purpose. Any publication may include technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. We do not warrant that such documents, related graphics and materials will be uninterrupted or error-free, that defects will be corrected or that this Site, or the server that makes it available, are free of viruses or other harmful components. Communications sent on this Site on the Internet are not secure and are deemed NOT confidential. Users should not send sensitive or confidential information.
BY ACCESSING THE SITE, YOU UNDERSTAND THAT YOU MAY BE WAIVING RIGHTS WITH RESPECT TO CLAIMS THAT ARE AT THIS TIME UNKNOWN OR UNSUSPECTED, AND IN ACCORDANCE WITH SUCH WAIVER, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTAND, AND HEREBY EXPRESSLY WAIVE, THE BENEFITS OF SECTION 1542 OF THE CIVIL CODE OF CALIFORNIA, AND ANY SIMILAR LAW OF ANY STATE OR TERRITORY, WHICH PROVIDES AS FOLLOWS: "A GENERAL RELEASE DOES NOT EXTEND TO CLAIMS WHICH THE CREDITOR DOES NOT KNOW OR SUSPECT TO EXIST IN HIS OR HER FAVOR AT THE TIME OF EXECUTING THE RELEASE, WHICH IF KNOWN BY HIM OR HER MUST HAVE MATERIALLY AFFECTED HIS OR HER SETTLEMENT WITH THE DEBTOR."
Privacy.  Personal information transmitted to Us will be treated in accordance with Our Privacy Policy (see Privacy Policy below.)
Our Copyrighted Materials; Infringement Claims.  The copyrights in all text, images, screens and other materials provided on this Site (collectively, the "Materials") are owned by Us and/or by third parties. Except as provided below, none of the Materials may be copied, distributed, displayed, downloaded, or transmitted in any form or by any means without the prior written permission of Us or the copyright owner.  We hereby authorize you to view and print the documents, related graphics and materials published by Us on this Site subject to the following conditions:
use is for non-commercial or personal purposes;
use is for informational purposes only;
no documents, related graphics or materials available from this Site or other sites linked to one of our sites are modified in any way; and
no graphics available from this site are used separate from the accompanying text.
In consideration of this authorization, you agree that the above copyright notice and this permission notice shall appear in all copies of any documents, related graphics and materials, or any portions thereof, published on this Site.  Modification or use of the Materials, or any portion thereof, published on this Site for any other purpose than indicated herein, is a violation of Our copyright and other proprietary rights. The use of any documents, related graphics and materials from this Site or any networked computer environment is prohibited.   Any product, service, process or technology described in this Site is the subject of other intellectual property rights reserved by Us and may not be licensed hereunder. Any rights not expressly granted herein are reserved.
Unauthorized use of any Materials contained on this Site may violate copyright laws, trademark laws, the laws of privacy and publicity, and/or other regulations and statutes.  If you believe that any of the Materials infringe on any of your intellectual property rights, please contact Us immediately at the address provided below.  Except as expressly provided herein, We and the third parties reserve all rights with respect to the Materials, and may pursue all legally available options under both civil and criminal laws (and may cooperate with law enforcement agencies) in the event of any violations.
Trademarks.  Trademarks and service marks that may be referred to on this Site are Our property or the property of their respective owners. Nothing on this Site should be construed as granting, by implication, estoppel, or otherwise, any license or right to use any trademark without Our written permission. Our name or logo may not be used in any way, including in advertising or publicity pertaining to distribution of materials on this Site, without prior written permission. You are not authorized to use Our logo as a hyperlink to this Site unless you obtain Our written permission in advance.
Prohibited Actions.  You agree not to:  (a) decompile, reverse engineer, disassemble, modify, reduce the Site to human perceivable form or create derivative works based upon the Site or any part thereof; (b) disable any licensing or control features of the Site; (c) “frame” the Site or any portion thereof or otherwise cause the Site or its contents to appear to be provided by anyone except Us; (d) introduce into the Site any virus or other code or routine intended to disrupt or damage the Site, or alter, damage or delete any Materials, or retrieve or record information about the Site or its users; (e) merge the Site or Materials with another program or create derivative works based on the Site or Materials; (f) remove, obscure, or alter any notice of the copyright or other proprietary legends on the Site or Materials; (g) sublicense, assign, translate, rent, lease, lend, resell for profit, distribute or otherwise assign or transfer the Materials or access to the Site to others; (h) use, or allow the use of, the Site or the Materials in contravention of any federal, state, local, foreign or other applicable law, or rules or regulations of regulatory or administrative organizations; or (i) otherwise act in a fraudulent, illegal, malicious or negligent manner when using the Site.  Except as expressly provided herein, We and the third parties reserve all rights with respect to the Site, and may pursue all legally available options under both civil and criminal laws (and may cooperate with law enforcement agencies) in the event of any violations.
Prohibition on Scripts, Bots, Third Parties, etc.  You shall not access or use the Site by means of any automated program, expert system, electronic agent or “bot,” and shall not give any person or entity access to the Site.
Prohibition on Scraping.  You are prohibited from “scraping,” copying, republishing, licensing, or selling the data or information on the Site if you do so for commercial purposes.
Ownership of Usage Data.  We may collect and aggregate data about your usage of the Site, and We shall be the sole owner of such information.  See also our Privacy Policy regarding the use of cookies, on our site.
Links.  Although We control a few hyperlinks in the Site that relate to Our affiliated companies, some links within this Site may lead to third-party sites. We include these third-party links solely as a convenience to you.  We cannot vouch for or take responsibility for the information contained in any such sites or information sources. The presence of a link does not imply an endorsement of the linked site, its operator, or its contents, or that We are in any way affiliated with the linked site. The Site does not incorporate any materials appearing in such linked sites by reference.  We reserve the right to terminate a link to a third party web site at any time.  The third party sites are not controlled by Us, and may have different terms of use and privacy policies, which We encourage you to review.
Must Be At Least 18 Years Old to Use This Site.  At this Site We make no active effort to collect personal information from individuals under the age of eighteen (18).  We require that Site users be of legal age to enter into agreements (typically, at least eighteen (18) years of age or older).
Governing Law.  For Canadian residents, these Terms and Conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Province of Québec and Canada applicable therein, without giving effect to any principles of conflict of law.  For United States  residents, these Terms and Conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Delaware and the United States, as applicable, without giving effect to any principles of conflict of law.
Not Authorized to Do Business In Every Jurisdiction.  We are not authorized to do business in every jurisdiction.  Information published on this Site may contain references or cross-references to goods or services that are not available in your province/state or country.
Entire Agreement; Severability.  You acknowledge that you have read and understood these Terms and Conditions and that you agree to be bound by its terms and conditions.  You further agree that these Terms and Conditions, together with the Privacy Policy, which is hereby incorporated into these Terms and Conditions by reference, constitute the complete and exclusive statement of these Terms and Conditions between you and Us and supersedes all other proposals or prior agreements oral or written, and any other communications relating to the subject matter of these Terms and Conditions.  If any provision of these Terms and Conditions is found unenforceable, it shall not affect the validity of these Terms and Conditions, which shall remain valid and enforceable according to its terms.
Contact Us.  For further information, or inquiries about these Terms and Conditions, please contact:
Communications Department,
395 de Maisonneuve Blvd. West
Montreal, QC  H3A 1L6
Canada
Email:  communications@domtar.com
Last Updated: May 2020
Privacy Policy
Domtar Corporation ("Domtar") is committed to and recognizes your need for protection and privacy issues on the Internet.
In general, you can visit  Domtar.com Web site ("Website") without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. We may collect the IP addresses and / or domain names of visitors for site administration purposes, such as to analyze this data for trends and statistics. No personal information is obtained, but the patterns of usage may be tracked and monitored.
COLLECTING PERSONAL IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION
There are times when we may collect personal information from you; for example, when you are sending an information request.
We may collect the following information from you voluntarily:
Name
Company
Email address
Phone number
REMOVING OR UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION
If you change your mind or wish to update personal information, we will endeavor to correct, update or remove the personal data you give us. You may at any time revise your personal information or question it by directly contacting us at communications@domtar.com.
Domtar reserves the right to disclose user information in special cases, when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other Web site users or anyone else who could be harmed by such activities. We may disclose personal information in response to a subpoena, when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or to respond to an emergency situation.
Contact Information
Corporate Offices
234 Kingsley Park Drive
Fort Mill SC 29715
United States
1-803-802-7500
1-877-877-4685
395 de Maisonneuve Blvd West
(PDF)
2019 Sustainability Report
(PDF)
Corporate Fact Sheet
(PDF)
© Domtar Corporation 2020. All rights reserved.
Terms & Conditions / Privacy
Employee Access
404 Error
Oops, we recently updated our web site and it looks like this page has been recycled. Please use our search feature to find what you are looking for.
Close
